<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Machine Learning - Category - YOUHEE</title>
        <link>http://youheekil.github.io/categories/machine-learning/</link>
        <description>Machine Learning - Category - YOUHEE</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><managingEditor>youhee.kil@gmail.com (Youhee Kil)</managingEditor>
            <webMaster>youhee.kil@gmail.com (Youhee Kil)</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 00:00:00 &#43;0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://youheekil.github.io/categories/machine-learning/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>[Machine Learning] Basic Math for ML with Python (Part 1)</title>
    <link>http://youheekil.github.io/machine-learning-basic-math_pt1/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Youhee</author>
    <guid>http://youheekil.github.io/machine-learning-basic-math_pt1/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Machine learning is nothing but a geometry problem ! All data is the same. Understanding geometry is very important to solve machine learning problems.
 [Numpy] Basic Linear Algebra Linear algebra, mathematical discipline that deals with vectors and matrices and, more generally, with vector spaces and linear transformations (Britannica)
In this lecture, you will learn
 Scala, Vector, Array, Tensor Dot product &amp; Norm Multiplication &amp; Transpose &amp; Invertible matrix Linear Transformation Eigen Value &amp; Eigen Vector Cosine Similarity  and perform these with Numpy]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>[Udacity] MLOps</title>
    <link>http://youheekil.github.io/udacity-mlops/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 13:38:13 &#43;0900</pubDate>
    <author>Youhee</author>
    <guid>http://youheekil.github.io/udacity-mlops/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Udacity Program   MLOps   I participated Machine Learning DevOps Engineer program in Udacity (Certification).
The program was extraordinary great, providing handful hands-on projects with the detailed and accurate human feedback. MLOps was whole different world and opened my eyes to the world of DevOps and machine learning in production level.
The program is consisted of four projects, and each project covered different technology skills and tools. The most important thing the program emphasized was clean code principes, such as refactoring, handling errors, unit-testing, logging, and addressing.]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
